(Leonard:)So, what do you guys think?
No, pretty much any way I say that
is gonna hurt his feelings.
(Leonard:)Okay, what's wrong with it?
(Leonard:)- What's wrong with it?
- Not you. I wasn't asking you.
(Leonard:)- Penny?
- Well, it's a little juvenile.
(Penny:)I mean, it kind of looks like
the MySpace page of a 13-year-old girl.
(Leonard:)No, it doesn't.
(Howard:)Please. Dateline could use it
to attract predators.
(Sheldon:)Penny, this is your enterprise,
so it's ultimately your decision.
(Sheldon:)But based on the quality of his work,
I'd strongly recommend...
(Sheldon:)...that we let Leonard go.
You wanna fire me?
(Sheldon:)What I want is irrelevant.
This is Penny's decision.
(Leonard:)Penny?
Excuse me, if I did such a bad job,
then why do we already have orders?